I mean, it's still strong.
Black spin.
This is when we take some time to just flex our muscles and, you know,
our heart on our favorite genre, hip hop.
We're talking jazzy, the jazzy era of hip hop,
where there were so many songs that came out with jazz samples,
horns, trumpets, all those types of things.
What were some of your favorites from that era?
Number one, number one, number one,
when they reminisce over you, my God.
You know that that's my favorite sample of all time.
Anyway, also stakes is high.
I see.
Once I saw the thread, cause I love stakes is high.
Like the album and that record.
And I was like, I mean, come on, it's Dilla, but it is a jazz sample.
But I mean,
the more obvious ones are like passing me by or not even we got the jazz.
Um, did you like the one,
what was the one by guru that was like,
the girls look so good.
Ex-girl to the next girl.
Come on.
That's my record.
We are.